pantheon.org 2019-10-16

# Privacy Policy | Encyclopedia Mythica

_Respecting the privacy of our visitors is important to us. Read this page to learn about personal information that Encyclopedia Mythica collects and how it may be used._

## Information Collected By Encyclopedia Mythica

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our users:

  1. ### Information You Provide To Us

We receive and store any information you chose to enter on our website or provide to us in any other way (such as via the contact form). You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but this might limit interaction.

  2. ### Automatic Information

    * We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Encyclopedia Mythica automatically receives and records certain "traffic data" on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. Encyclopedia Mythica uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website.
    * Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. These can be found through a simple internet search.

## E-mail Communications

Encyclopedia Mythica is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party, period. We do not send out any e-mails or notifications whatsoever.

## Cookies

  * Cookies are small text files stored by your browser on your computer when you visit a website. We use cookies to improve our website and make it easier to use. Cookies permit us to recognize you and avoid repetitive requests for the same information. Encyclopedia Mythica cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information. Most browsers will accept cookies until you change your browser settings to refuse them. You may change your browser's settings to refuse our cookies.
  * The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated.
  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to this website.
  * Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

## Children

Our service are intended solely for persons 13 years of age and older. If you are under the age of 13 you may not access or use our service. By using our service you represent and warrant to us that you are 13 years of age or older.

## Links To Third Party Web Sites

Our service may contain links to other websites and software. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these websites or software. Please visit the privacy policies of these third party sites in order o understand their privacy and information collection practices.

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

Encyclopedia Mythica may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Encyclopedia Mythica website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

## Conditions Of Use

If you decide to visit Encyclopedia Mythica website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of Dutch law.

## Effective date of this privacy policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of November 1, 2005 and last updated June 22, 2009.
